zlobos.com 2001-09-03

# zlobos.com: Privacy Policy

zUniversity.com, Inc. (“zUniversity”) has created this privacy statement to explain why certain information about you is collected and how your personal privacy will be protected within our portal Web site. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices of zUniversity and the University/Alumni Association (the “Affiliate”) affiliated with the portal web site (the “Site”).  zUniversity reserves the right to change this policy at any time by posting a new privacy policy at this location.  zUniversity is proud to provide you access to the Site where we strive to bring you some of the best content and services available on the Web.  In so doing, we have enlisted various content and service providers who are not affiliated with zUniversity or the Affiliate to bring you content including and services including e-mail, e-commerce services and personal planning tools. As such content and services are provided by third parties, and not by zUniversity or the Affiliate, those areas of the Site where such content and services are available, and where third parties may collect information about you, shall be governed by the privacy policies of those third parties. Such third party privacy policies shall be accessible from those areas of the Site.  This privacy policy sets forth the privacy practices involving those portions of the Site directly provided by zUniversity and/or the Affiliate.  BY ACCESSING THE SITE, YOU ACCEPT, WITHOUT LIMITATION OR QUALIFICATION, ALL OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THOSE AREAS OF THE SITE WHERE INFORMATION IS COLLECTED BY THIRD PARTIES IS SUBJECT TO THE PRIVACY POLICIES OF THOSE THIRD PARTIES AND NOT ZUNIVERSITY OR THE AFFILIATE. ****

**_What Information We Collect and How We Use That Information:_**

**Contact Information** :  Some areas of our Site request or require contact and other information.  During the registration process, we collect personal and other information such as your name, address, and e-mail address.  Your contact information may be used to get in touch with you when necessary with respect to transactions conducted through the Site, material changes in our Site’s policies, or otherwise.  We do not share your contact information with any third party without your consent, except to a court or governmental agency or if otherwise required by law.  __

**Financial Information.   **Users making purchases on the Site are required to provide a valid credit card number and expiration date along with the name on the credit card, the corresponding billing address and the mailing address (if different), telephone number and e-mail address.  We use this information to provide you with the goods and services you order through our Site and such information may be shared with third party goods and services providers so that your purchase orders can be fulfilled.  To purchase goods and services through our Site, you must be 18 years of age or older. ****

**Demographic Information** :  Demographic and profile data (e.g., age, gender and income level) may also be collected at our Site.  Optional and other demographic may be shared with advertisers or other third parties on an aggregated basis.  We may also maintain a database of transactions on the Site and use this information in aggregate form to track the success of our Site.

**Internet Protocol Address:   **We collect an IP address from all visitors to our Site.  We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web Site. 

**_Use of cookies:_**

Our Site, like most Web sites, uses cookies to enhance your experience while using our Site.  Cookies are pieces of information that some Web sites transfer to the computer that is browsing that Web site and are used for record-keeping purposes at many Web sites.  Use of cookies makes Web-browsing easier by performing certain functions such as saving your passwords, your personal preferences regarding your use of the particular Web site and to make sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly.  Many consider the use of cookies to be an industry standard. 

Your browser is probably set to accept cookies.  However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies.  If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our Site will not function properly when you view them.

_**Public Forums:**_

This Site makes __ chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users.  Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**_Surveys, Contests and Sweepstakes:_**

To the extent that you choose to participate in any of our online surveys, contests or sweepstakes, you may be asked to volunteer certain information about yourself such as your name, zip code, age, income level, etc.  With respect to surveys, you may provide some, all, or none of the information as you so choose and such information shall be used to improve the Site as we add more features in accordance with your input.  With respect to contests and sweepstakes, we do ask that you submit your true identity and other information so that we may contact you, if necessary.  We may share such information with third parties to facilitate the delivery of prizes when such prizes are supplied by third parties.  The exact rules of our contests and sweepstakes will be posted and may vary from contest to contest.

**_Children:_**

zUniversity and the Affiliate take the protection of children seriously.  zUniversity and the Affiliate do not knowingly collect the personal information of children, send e-mails or other communications to children, or allow them to post messages in our chat rooms or on our bulletin boards.  zUniversity and the Affiliate do not knowingly entice children with special games, prizes or other rewards to divulge additional or superfluous information.  zUniversity and the Affiliate encourage parents and guardians to advise children to not offer personally identifiable information about themselves on the Internet.

**_Links to Third-Party Sites:_**

zUniversity and the Affiliate offer links to third party Web sites.  Any time you click on a link and are transported to a third party Web site, you should be aware that such third party Web site shall be governed by its own privacy policy, and not by the privacy policy of zUniversity.  We are committed to providing links to third parties whose privacy policies are as responsible and comprehensive as our own.  However, we cannot control the privacy practices of third parties and we encourage you to consult such policies prior to disclosing any information about yourself. 

**_Third-Party Advertising and Third-Party Cookies:_**

We use DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to service ads when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.  In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.  If you would like more information about these practices and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.doubleclick.net/naiprivacy) or visit <http://www.doubleclick.net/naiprivacy>. 

_**Security:**_

This Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

_**Choice/Opt-Out:**_

zUniversity and the Affiliate may send communications regarding its services, the Site or otherwise.  zUniversity and the Affiliate provide you the opportunity to opt-in to receiving such communications during the registration process and you may opt-out of receiving such communications at any time by indicating your desire to opt-out:

  1. in an email sent to [support@zuniversity.com](mailto:support@zuniversity.com), or
  2. by mail to the postal address located below. 

_**Correct/Update:**_

If any of your contact information changes or is incorrect, please email [support@zuniversity.com](mailto:support@zuniversity.com) with your new, correct information. 

_**Contacting the Web Site:**_

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, you can contact: 

Web Site Administrator  
c/o zUniversity.com  
258 Atlantic Street  
Stamford, CT 06901  

You can also send e-mail to [support@zuniversity.com](mailto:support@zuniversity.com).
